<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Basic Music Player</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_item_library_music">Music Library</string>
    <string name="nav_item_library_podcasts">Podcasts</string>
    <string name="nav_item_equalizer">EQ</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="label_eq_activity">Equalizer</string>
    <string name="label_music_library_activity">Music Library</string>
    <string name="label_podcast_library_activity">Podcasts</string>
    <string name="label_now_playing_activity">Now Playing</string>

    <string name="equalizer_activity_description">
        This activity will contain GUI components to interact with an object
        of the Equalizer class in android.media.audiofx.

    </string>

    <string name="music_library_activity_description">
        This activity will first show the tab including all tracks in alphabetical
        order.  When each track is clicked, the user is taken to the now playing
        activity to see the track album artwork, progress bar, play/pause buttons, etc.
        other tabs will be added in future to categorize tracks by artist, album, and genre.
        In order to play the files locally from the system, a MediaPlayer object must be
        instantiated (android.media.MediaPlayer)
    </string>

    <string name="podcast_library_activity_description">
        This activity will first show the tab including all tracks in alphabetical
        order.  When each track is clicked, the user is taken to the now playing
        activity to see the track album artwork, progress bar, play/pause buttons, etc.
        other tabs will be added in future to categorize tracks by podcast and genre.
        In order to play the files locally from the system, a MediaPlayer object must be
        instantiated (android.media.MediaPlayer)
    </string>

    <string name="home_screen_activity_description">
        This activity is the first place the user lands.  There will not be anything on this
        screen except for a GUI that looks like radio dials (goofy design, but fun).  It will not
        actually be a functioning radio, rather the gimmick is that it will have the nostalgic
        feel of a radio while really just being a player for the library/podcasts all on shuffle.
        There will be a \"tune\" dial which just switches between genres, a volume slider, am/fm
        switch to change between music and podcasts.
    </string>

    <string name="now_playing_activity_description">
        This activity would be an imageview of the album cover artwork for a given song or podcast.
        Additionally the GUI would include play, fastforward, rewind buttons and a status/seekbar
        to traverse the media as it plays. The user should be able to swipe the image in order
        to skip to the next song or go back to the last one.


    </string>

</resources>
